Welcome to English in a Minute. Most people enjoy going to parties. You get to be around
friends, eat food, and maybe listen to music. But do your parties ever have animals?
Party animal.
Hey Jonathan, are you as ready as I am for the weekend?
Oh yeah. I'm going to my brother's birthday party on Friday. My cousin is having her graduation
party Saturday and I'm hosting the karaoke party on Sunday.
Wow, you are quite the party animal, aren't you?
That's nothing. You should have seen me in college.
A party animal is not an actual animal. It is a person who really enjoys going to parties.
Most of their time is spent finding out where the latest and best party is going to be.
And that's English in a minute.
(upbeat music)