Hello, everyone, I am Buyi.
This class will introduce a tool called
Use the TrueGPT Automation Developer
Create a coming message
I will explain the three important things later.
The first is why the code is called "GPT"
Let's introduce the TrueGPT
How to use it
Let's talk about the latest one.
I use the new one.
OK, everyone should not be unfamiliar with TrueGPT
Currently, it is AI, AIGC, AI Generator, Content
At present, when it comes to red-grinding machine
All the software development workers in the world are thinking about
How to use TrueGPT to help us develop the entire software process
Or improve our environment
And I am most important here
Use TrueGPT to write the KitKartMessage
How to write the KitKartMessage
You can refer to this article
I will put it in the link below
I directly use the source
The source is called CodeGPT
If you like it, you can share it with me
The main point is to help the software development
You can see CodeGPT creates the KitKartMessage effect
You write the code first
You have to write the KitKartMessage
For example, what does this function do
Or how do I solve this bug
You may want to say how to write the content
Let everyone know when they check
After we have CodeGPT
We use AI to help you see the whole KitKartMessage
We help to automatically create this content
You see this is the bottom effect
You see all the KartMessage here
All use this tool called CodeGPT
Help me create
Not me
Basically, 8 or 9% is correct
Basically, if you want to slightly tweak yourself
You can do the effect you want
Basically, if you have a long time to enter the code
That's also because I hope that the KartMessage you write
Is helpful to the team
This tool can help you to reduce a lot of time
Ok, then
I don't want to write CodeGPT
In fact, the KitKart platform has already
Similar tools like this
Why do you want to re-develop it
The first one is the cross-platform platform
I need to use the source
To avoid the different platforms and different environments
This is easier for developers who do not receive the environment
The second one is that my future plan is
The next GitHub, GitHub, Bbac and other platforms
After sending PR, you can automatically help
Help to organize the content of KartMessage
And automatically leave a message
Then this tool
So my development tool is not just a single developer
Can automatically create KartMessage
In the future, I hope that the whole
Can be motivated to help to do the code
Then the third reason is that in the future
I hope it's not just an open AI API
The current API of TrueGPT
Currently in Azure's API
Open AI has been supported
Next, let's talk about how to use it
Actually, it's very simple
Every time, the number of users will have
The corresponding self-sufficiency file of Linux, Mac OS Windows
You just need to send it to BIN
Then go to Open AI's website
Create an API key
Every month seems to be free 18 dollars
But I think this is already cheap
In fact, every day, you know
No matter how much you pay
3.5 turbo version is actually very cheap
So basically
KartMessage
Look at the token amount he has seen
Actually not even a dollar
It's quite cheap, so everyone's credit card is right
Because for you
It's very useful to write KartMessage
And you don't have to waste time to
The things you wrote
Okay, then
After everyone is done, you can use
We can install it
Let's take a look at this website
Ok, it's easy
You can download from this list
To the corresponding self-sufficiency file
You can download
The answer for your AUN 64 and AMD 64
Or Linux version
Or Windows version can be
Or you can say that you are very simple
If you use Mac, you can
You can use Blue install
Basically, it's blue tab
Apple Boy's Latch tab
Then install
Next is how to use
Set up your API key
It's really easy to use it
You can continue to use it after you create your API key
You just need to export this variable
Next, you will do the post-sale thing
Let's see how to use it at the bottom
Let's take a look
Let's take a look at the current
Communion
Because it's here
I changed something
Let's take a look at the GIT leaf
After I changed this
Let's take a look at it
Let's set it to
3 states
Next we have a code GPT
You can play hlp
You can see that it has many
Cami can be used
The first Cami
It will help you to auto-john
Then you can set your own camera
Let me introduce this a little bit
Then you can also use the GIT method
This is less useful
It will help you to set up a GIT hook
Under your GIT
To change your Cami hook
Then you can automatically
Go to the message you sent
Then there is a most important function
It can go to the remote control
So I will introduce it later
Let's take a look at it
We are now in a stage state
There is a CND
I have changed this answer
In fact, it is to
Change a constant
Change it to a
The address of your own address
Then we use the code GPT Cami
So it will automatically
Use GPT 3.5's turbo version
After that, it will tell you
What is the summary of Cami
It will tell you the environment
Preface for consistency
Then it will tell you
The content inside it is
I changed the Github
Change the weight to the bottom
After that, it will write to you
Cami message
It automatically sends you Cami
So you can see that you are automatically changed
Like this
If you are not satisfied with this message
You can use another way
You can go to this
This is actually the same as your GIT Cami
You will go to the message of Cami
The message of Cami
The next step is to perform
GPT 3.5's turbo version
After that, it will go to
Change a new message
Until you change it
The message you want
So you can keep changing it
Of course, it will sign
The money of your calculation
So you see here, I tell you
How much is your PON token
Then how much is your comp
How much is the token used
Then the total token is these two
That's the last thing you want to pay
Now every 1000 tokens is 0.002
That's very cheap
So basically you use a lot of money every day
Almost not much
So you can save every day
To pay for the drinks
How much is your day saved
Cami message time
So I think it's pretty convenient
Let's look at the other parameters
How to use
In fact, we can go through a
Code GPT to use
Very hot time to set up some
Environmental data
After I wrote down the Open API
Basically, I don't have to
Go to eSports anymore
Because it will directly occupy
The code GPT
Code GPT.yaml
Write in this value
So basically you don't have to worry about it
Then openAI
OpenAI has a parameter
Basis, you are here now
Why this parameter is like this
You see now almost all companies
OpenAI's net worth is all blocked
After that, everyone is crazy
Fullyå‡ set
Fully Plastic
You can change this point to the best UI
I guess at the beginning
OpenAI should have found this problem
When the record is released
He told me that he can
Everyone can change the best UI
So you can change it to what you want
You can use this free
Many people think that my key is stolen
What are you doing
If I don't believe it, I can just go and add it myself
It's a Chinese developer
Then it's a Dino developer
Okay, then you can
Some data
API key
And your organization
There are more organizations in your account
Remember to set this
Then you can use the model you want to use
You can now use GPT 3.5
Turbo or you need
A lot of tokens because GP3.5
His token is the token of 409
Then you can change it to GPT4
Maybe you can use 8k tokens
Or 32k tokens
But his fee is
One is 15 times, one is 30 times
So please be careful
If you need it
If you just want to do the terminal
GPT 3.5 terminal is very useful
Then in terms of language
You basically use English
You can change your terminal
Translate into Chinese
Translate into Chinese, translate into Chinese and Japanese
The point is to use these three
Then I wrote a
Plastic function here
Or sake in the way of doing connection
So you have been doing these
Sake and Plastic
You can connect it in this way
Then it's time out
This time out is to assume your
Your token needs to look a lot
Sometimes
OpenAI will be noisy because OpenAI is too much
So sometimes it's very slow
So you just adjust this time
Then there is Miss Token
This token is that
When you reply
These words are too sour
In this token
If you don't use the token
You can increase it from here
The default is 300
But the main thing is that
When you are doing code review, you need this
good
Then there is also temperature
This is the basic parameters of OpenAI
0.7
0.0 to 0.2
Then the answer will be more and more
So don't be too high or too low
So 0.7 should be the parameters of this network
There is also a called
Diff Unify
I will add this
You can look at it
You will see that
My Diff Nino has
The front and the back are all leaked
This is the thing that the Git predicted
But your Diff Nino
So it's growing in the Diff
Suppose your Git Diff
If you put this Unify color as 0
Basically
It will only leak this red and green
Can we try
Basically it has a
There is a Diff thing
Anyway, this is
This is basically the adjustment
Can you think about it
I want to see the front
How many rows are there with the back
The prediction is three rows
So basically you adjust it
If we send it to OpenAI
Can reduce the token amount
So this is also a good thing to reduce the token amount
So if your
Your Diff Nino is very long
Basically you can adjust it a little
Then you can save some tokens
I think you can set it as 0
Because
Basically OpenAI
Look at the front and the back
The whole answer is not very big
So basically I set it as 0
OK
Then there is Isqulist
I think this is very useful
What are you doing
Suppose you change things such as
Package.JSON
Package is
MPN
There is no use in that
Or in GO
For example, this GO GO
This thing is actually useless
Then send it to OpenAI
And then the token amount is occupied
So basically I will choose this
So similar to this
OK
For example, like this
Diff Unify
Then Isqulist
I set it for example
You have Taste of Fire
That basically
There is no meaning
We don't want to give OpenAI
We don't want to give AI to look
But it is in this token amount
We can just drop it
Basically this is the parameters
So this is what we just talked about
It can do
The preview of the token amount
You can also download the preview
The first thing is that I don't
Do this
Do the token amount on the token
Help you do the token amount
Then you basically have Stained Fire
Still in
Then this is to write your wrong translation
Basically don't use this function
Don't translate the code into Chinese
Because the token amount of Chinese is quite large
So everyone please use it
Then this is
Just demoed
If you are not satisfied with the first
The code content of the first card
You can keep downloading this command
You can continue to modify the last card
Then there is a user who told me before
This card content is a little bit different from the format
Change it
No problem
You can define this template
There are several parameters
Summary of Preface
Summary of Title
Summary of Message
You can use it
So you can download a
Template Stream
To change these things
Or Template Fire
You can set it up
Okay, it's not here to talk about the key
Install and Uninstall
Then you can
Get Add
After these fires
Next key card
It will jump out of a window
That is the window in the card
Then put the AI
The layer of the layer of AI
Go down
So you see it's going to help you do the code
So it's very simple
Then let's talk about a calling
That calling is not very easy
It's the same as the key card
Just say it doesn't help you do the code
It helps you do the call review
That's what it means
Okay, let's do the same
Let's take a look at an example
Suppose we let's take a look at this code
Okay
Let's go to the PHP file
Click on the front
HP
Okay
Then the same
Let's put the key card on it
Okay, let's take a look at this
How to use it
Code to the PHP
Okay
We are
Anyway, just use
Review
Let's do the next review
Okay
After the next review
It will go to the content in the Stage Fire
Then it will start to do the review code change
Then this is really
It needs to be spent a period of time
Then you can spray these
These reviews
In fact, this thing is actually very useful
The reviewer told you that it may have some
Some ingestion
So you have to go to
To verify your input and what
Enter the show as a card
So I think these
The tools are very useful
It's five points for you
So basically I hope this thing can be used
Our
The software is open
Every time the user posts a PR
For example, your team
The team is posting a PR
It's automatic
From your
From your card
All the content in it
Go to the code review
Give a summarize
That this summarize
Is very useful to you
For the developer
It's very useful to the developer
Then for the reviewer
He can look at this first
He can look at this review
Summon
You know that you
What are you doing with this whole code
And maybe some
What are the problems in the first
And what suggestions do you give
Basically
Usually need to say
He actually has some
Some ingestion
That's not you
But do you have to wait for you to fix it
I'll go and see
No problem
So basically I think
The suggestions given by AI
Are very, very useful
Not just in
Code
The code is very much
Because he almost
I've finished looking at the game
That's the data of 2021
Then I think that
The whole model base
Has been very, very strong
So basically
He can look at the language
Okay
That's what I'm going to introduce today
I think this is very useful
Then below is that
Okay
Then now it's China and Hong Kong
Actually
Most companies are strict about the transparency
So this tool
I just developed
Process function
Can be connected to the sake
You can connect through the process
Or go to
Ask OpenAI
Or if you have
If you have a base UI
You can add a form
Or pass it
It's okay
Okay
If you expect it
I think the next step
Is to open the whole of the age
After coming in
He will support
OpenAI
Age of OpenAI
Because OpenAI
The biggest share is
Microsoft
Microsoft is also
This thing
Combined with their
The whole age of the whole cloud service
So basically
We are
Most of the companies
It's impossible to go to the OpenAI
To do the same
Because he didn't have the ability to say
He won't take your data
Do any
The full-time work
But Microsoft
He is in this area
Is having the ability to say
We will never go
Where to go
To do that
This is the right thing
This is to sign with Microsoft
The contract after that
So this is
The big company is going to go to the right place
good
I hope
I hope that the introduction of this tool
Is helpful to everyone
If you like it
You can help me
Go to the new one
Click on the war
At present, in fact, I think
There are quite a lot of people using it
So now it's probably
More than 300 people
If you like it
Just help me introduce the goods
Promote
Thank you all